A Guide to the Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975., Extent: 366 boxes; 165 cubic feet. (Box 1-366)
  - 1935.
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1935 (Box 223)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Southern, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Valley, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Virginia Central, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Virginian, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1935 (Box 224)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1935 (Box 225)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1935 (Box 225)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1935 (Box 225)
    - Unidentified, 1935 (Box 225)
  - 1936.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1936 (Box 225)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1936 (Box 225)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1936 (Box 225)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1936 (Box 225)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1936 (Box 225)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Clinchfield, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Danville and Western, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Interstate, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1936 (Box 227)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1936 (Box 227)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1936 (Box 227)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1936 (Box 227)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1936 (Box 227)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1936 (Box 227)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1936 (Box 227)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell Transportation Company, 1936 (Box 227)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1936 (Box 228)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1936 (Box 228)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1936 (Box 228)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1936 (Box 228)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1936 (Box 228)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1936 (Box 228)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1936 (Box 228)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1936 (Box 228)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1936 (Box 229)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1936 (Box 229)
    - Southeastern Express Company (2 folders), 1936 (Box 229)
    - Southern, 1936 (Box 229)
    - Valley, 1936 (Box 229)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1936 (Box 229)
    - Virginia Central, 1936 (Box 229)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1936 (Box 229)
    - Virginian, 1936 (Box 230)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1936 (Box 230)
    - Washington and Old Dominion (2 folders), 1936 (Box 230)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1936 (Box 230)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1936 (Box 230)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1936 (Box 230)
  - 1937.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1937 (Box 230)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1937 (Box 230)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1937 (Box 231)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1937 (Box 231)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1937 (Box 231)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1937 (Box 231)
    - Clinchfield, 1937 (Box 231)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1937 (Box 231)
    - Danville and Western, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Interstate, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1937 (Box 232)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1937 (Box 232)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1937 (Box 233)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1937 (Box 233)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1937 (Box 233)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1937 (Box 233)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell Transportation Company, 1937 (Box 233)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1937 (Box 233)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1937 (Box 233)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1937 (Box 233)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1937 (Box 234)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1937 (Box 234)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1937 (Box 234)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1937 (Box 234)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1937 (Box 234)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1937 (Box 234)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1937 (Box 234)
    - Southeastern Express Company (2 folders), 1937 (Box 234)
    - Southern Railway, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Valley, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge (2 folders), 1937 (Box 235)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Virginia Central, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Virginian, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1937 (Box 235)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1937 (Box 236)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1937 (Box 236)
  - 1938.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1938 (Box 236)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1938 (Box 236)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1938 (Box 236)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1938 (Box 236)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1938 (Box 236)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1938 (Box 236)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1938 (Box 236)
    - Clinchfield, 1938 (Box 237)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg (2 folders), 1938 (Box 237)
    - Danville and Western, 1938 (Box 237)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1938 (Box 237)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1938 (Box 237)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1938 (Box 237)
    - Interstate, 1938 (Box 237)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1938 (Box 237)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1938 (Box 238)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1938 (Box 238)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk (2 folders), 1938 (Box 238)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1938 (Box 238)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1938 (Box 238)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1938 (Box 238)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1938 (Box 238)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell Transportation Company, 1938 (Box 238)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1938 (Box 238)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1938 (Box 239)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1938 (Box 239)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1938 (Box 239)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1938 (Box 239)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1938 (Box 239)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1938 (Box 239)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1938 (Box 239)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Southeastern Express Company (2 folders), 1938 (Box 240)
    - Southern, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Valley, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Virginia Central, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Virginian, 1938 (Box 240)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1938 (Box 241)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1938 (Box 241)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1938 (Box 241)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1938 (Box 241)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1938 (Box 241)
  - 1939.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1939 (Box 241)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1939 (Box 241)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1939 (Box 241)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1939 (Box 241)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Clinchfield, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg; Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia; New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Danville and Western, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Interstate, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1939 (Box 242)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell Transportation Company, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1939 (Box 243)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1939 (Box 243)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Southern, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Valley, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Virginia Central, 1939 (Box 244)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1939 (Box 245)
    - Virginian, 1939 (Box 245)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1939 (Box 245)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1939 (Box 245)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1939 (Box 245)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1939 (Box 245)
    - Winchester and Wardernsville, 1939 (Box 245)
  - 1940.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1940 (Box 245)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield and Ohio, 1940 (Box 245)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Clinchfield, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg; Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia; New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Danville and Western, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Interstate, 1940 (Box 246)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1940 (Box 247)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Southern, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Valley, 1940 (Box 248)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Virginian, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1940 (Box 249)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1940 (Box 249)
  - 1941.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1941 (Box 249)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1941 (Box 249)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Clinchfield, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg; Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia; New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Danville and Western, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1941 (Box 250)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Interstate, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Lynchburg Transit Company, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1941 (Box 251)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1941 (Box 252)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1941 (Box 252)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1941 (Box 252)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1941 (Box 252)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1941 (Box 252)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1941 (Box 252)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1941 (Box 252)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1941 (Box 252)
    - Southern, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Valley, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Virginia Central (2 folders), 1941 (Box 253)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Virginian, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Virginia Public Service Corporation, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1941 (Box 253)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1941 (Box 254)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1941 (Box 254)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1941 (Box 254)
    - Winchester and Western, 1941 (Box 254)
  - 1942.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1942 (Box 254)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1942 (Box 254)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1942 (Box 254)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1942 (Box 254)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1942 (Box 254)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Clinchfield, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg; Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia; New York, Philadelphia and Norfolk, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Danville and Western, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Danville Tranction and Power Company, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Interstate, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1942 (Box 255)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth, 1942 (Box 256)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1942 (Box 256)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1942 (Box 256)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1942 (Box 256)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1942 (Box 256)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1942 (Box 256)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1942 (Box 256)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Southern, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Valley, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1942 (Box 257)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Virginia Central, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Virginian, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1942 (Box 258)
    - Winchester and Western, 1942 (Box 258)
  - 1943.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1943 (Box 258)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1943 (Box 258)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Clinchfield, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg; Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia; New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Danville and Western, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1943 (Box 259)
    - Interstate, 1943 (Box 260)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1943 (Box 260)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1943 (Box 260)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1943 (Box 260)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1943 (Box 260)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1943 (Box 260)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1943 (Box 260)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1943 (Box 260)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Roanoke Railway and Connecting Company, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Southern, 1943 (Box 261)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Virginia Central, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Virginian, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1943 (Box 262)
    - Winchester and Western, 1943 (Box 262)
  - 1944.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Clinchfield, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg; Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia; New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1944 (Box 263)
    - Danville and Western, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Interstate, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1944 (Box 264)
    - Pennsylvania, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1944 (Box 265)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1944 (Box 265)
    - Southern, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Virginia Central, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Virginian, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Virginia Transit Company, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1944 (Box 266)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1944 (Box 267)
    - Winchester and Western, 1944 (Box 267)
  - 1945.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1945 (Box 267)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1945 (Box 267)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1945 (Box 267)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1945 (Box 267)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1945 (Box 267)
    - Citizens Rapid Transit Company, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Clinchfield, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg; Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia; New YOrk, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Danville and Western, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Interstate, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1945 (Box 268)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1945 (Box 269)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1945 (Box 269)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1945 (Box 269)
    - Pennsylvania, 1945 (Box 269)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1945 (Box 269)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1945 (Box 269)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1945 (Box 269)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Southern, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Virginia Central, 1945 (Box 270)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1945 (Box 271)
    - Virginian, 1945 (Box 271)
    - Virginia Transit Company, 1945 (Box 271)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1945 (Box 271)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1945 (Box 271)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1945 (Box 271)
    - Winchester and Western, 1945 (Box 271)
  - 1946.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1946 (Box 271)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1946 (Box 271)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Citizens Rapid Transit Company, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Clinchfield, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Danville and Western, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Interstate, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1946 (Box 273)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1946 (Box 273)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1946 (Box 273)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1946 (Box 273)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1946 (Box 272)
    - Pennsylvania, 1946 (Box 273)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1946 (Box 273)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1946 (Box 273)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1946 (Box 274)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1946 (Box 276)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1946 (Box 276)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1946 (Box 276)
    - Seaboard Air line (2 folders), 1946 (Box 276)
    - Southern, 1946 (Box 276)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Virginia Central, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Virginian, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Virginia Transit Company, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1946 (Box 277)
    - Winchester and Western, 1946 (Box 277)
  - 1947.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1947 (Box 276)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1947 (Box 276)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1947 (Box 276)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1947 (Box 276)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1947 (Box 276)
    - Clinchfield, 1947 (Box 276)
    - Danville and Western, 1947 (Box 276)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Interstate, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1947 (Box 277)
    - Pennsylvania, 1947 (Box 278)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1947 (Box 278)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1947 (Box 278)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1947 (Box 278)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1947 (Box 278)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1947 (Box 278)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1947 (Box 278)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Southern, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Swords Creek, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Virginia Central, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Virginian, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Virginia Transit Company, 1947 (Box 279)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1947 (Box 280)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1947 (Box 280)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1947 (Box 280)
    - Winchester and Western, 1947 (Box 280)
  - 1948.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1948 (Box 280)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1948 (Box 280)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1948 (Box 280)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1948 (Box 280)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1948 (Box 281)
    - Clinchfield, 1948 (Box 281)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1948 (Box 281)
    - Interstate, 1948 (Box 281)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1948 (Box 281)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1948 (Box 281)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1948 (Box 281)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1948 (Box 282)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1948 (Box 282)